I'm Jake O'Neill
我是杰克·奥尼尔
creator of animagraphs
动画创作者
and this is how a Formula 1 race car works
这就是一级方程式赛车的工作原理
let's start with aerodynamics
让我们从空气动力学开始
which is how the car interacts with
这就是汽车与
and moves through the air around it
并在它周围的空气中移动
it's best to focus on overall theory here
在这里最好专注于整体理论
to avoid getting lost
以避免迷路
in the absolute maze of individual
在个人的绝对迷宫中
aerodynamic features
气动特性
the front wing curves upward
前翼向上弯曲
forcing air to move around it in such a way
迫使空气以这种方式在它周围移动
that a high pressure area forms above the wing
机翼上方形成一个高压区
with lower pressure beneath
下面的压力较低
this pressure difference
这个压差
contributes to a kind of suction force
产生一种吸力
called down force
调降力
that pushes or sticks the car to the track
将汽车推或粘在轨道上
where the wing ends
翅膀的末端
and these different pressure zones meet
这些不同的压力区相遇
the air crashes into itself
空气撞击自己
creating a spiraling vortex
形成螺旋漩涡
vortices cause drag
涡流导致阻力
which tugs at the car slowing it down
拖着车减速
a cap on the wingtip
翼尖上的帽子
interrupts vortex formation for a less intense effect
中断漩涡形成以获得不太强烈的效果
in contrast the pointed
相比之下，尖的
curved in surfaces on the inside edge of the wing
机翼内侧边缘的曲面
intentionally shape
有意塑造
and direct a vortex around the floor of the car
并在汽车地板周围引导漩涡
sealing in the clean air that passes beneath
密封在下面经过的干净空气中
so while vortices do cause drag
所以虽然漩涡确实会产生阻力
they're also a useful tool to separate
它们也是分离的有用工具
and seal in different areas of air flow
并密封在不同的气流区域
as a matter of tradition
作为传统
F1 cars don't have fenders
F1赛车没有挡泥板
and the open spinning wheel and tire combination
还有开放式纺车轮和轮胎组合
is a major source of dirty turbulent air
是肮脏湍流空气的主要来源
turbulent air is unpredictable
湍流的空气变幻莫测
and not very useful for aerodynamic goals
对空气动力学目标不是很有用
like generating downforce
就像产生下压力一样
directly behind the tires
就在轮胎后面
the barge boards condition or clean up
驳船板保养或清理
some of this air flow
一些气流
while also pushing lots of dirty air
同时也推动了大量的脏空气
away from the body
远离身体
the narrow gap between the car floor and the track
汽车地板和轨道之间的狭窄缝隙
turns the entire floor into a giant
把整个地板变成一个巨大的
downforce generator
下压力发生器
as air squeezes
随着空气的挤压
thins and rushes beneath the car
在汽车下面变薄和匆忙
at a different rate and pressure than overhead air
以不同于头顶空气的速度和压力
the floor has a forward tilt or Rake
地板有向前倾斜或耙
that creates very low pressure at its narrowest point
在最窄处产生非常低的气压
but allows air to
但允许空气
more smoothly rejoin ambient air pressure
更平稳地重新加入环境气压
as it flows out the back
当它从后面流出时
a diffuser at the rear amplifies this goal
后部的扩散器放大了这一目标
with its more pronounced upward curvature
具有更明显的向上曲率
the diffuser has vertical veins
扩散器有垂直静脉
to control and direct
控制和指挥
the massive vortices that form behind the car
汽车后面形成的巨大漩涡
as air pours out from underneath
当空气从下面涌出
clean air is directed
清洁空气是直接的
into the side pods for cooling purposes
放入侧舱以供冷却
this stream passes through the car and out the back
这条小溪穿过汽车从后面流出
beneath the rear wing
尾翼下方
the smoothly contoured body guides
轮廓流畅的车身导轨
air streams gracefully around bodywork
气流优雅地围绕车身流动
for predictable handling under extreme conditions
在极端条件下可预测的处理
the upward curved rear wing
向上弯曲的尾翼
which is another critical downforce generator
这是另一个关键的下压力发生器
has notched end caps with gaps and louvers
具有带间隙和百叶窗的缺口端盖
to allow some air to combine early
让一些空气提前结合
altering and shaping rear wing vortex characteristics
改变和塑造后翼涡流特性
it's also where in wet conditions the noticeable
它也是在潮湿的条件下
Misty wingtip vortices sometimes appear in plain sight
模糊的翼尖漩涡有时会出现在视线中
a hydraulic actuator tilts a section of the rear wing
液压执行器倾斜尾翼的一部分
when the drag reduction system or Drs is engaged
当减阻系统或Drs启动时
generating less rear downforce
产生更少的后下压力
but allowing higher overall speed
但允许更高的整体速度
the massive area of dirty air
大片肮脏的空气
behind the car
在车后面
can make it difficult for other cars to approach
会让其他车很难靠近
and overtake
并超车
it's worth noting here that in coming years
值得注意的是，在未来几年
the aerodynamic design regulations for F1
F1的空气动力学设计规定
cars are set for major changes
汽车将迎来重大变革
to encourage closer racing and overtaking
鼓励更近距离的比赛和超车
the airflow pattern
气流模式
might look more like this than the current wide
可能看起来更像这样，而不是现在的宽
dirty wake
肮脏的尾流
now let's go underneath this exterior bodywork
现在让我们看看这个外部车身下面
starting with the core support structure
从核心支撑结构开始
a carbon fiber shell called a monocoque
一种叫做硬壳的碳纤维外壳
the engine heads and block
发动机头和发动机座
and the gearbox enclosure
和变速箱外壳
form the main structural support for all other systems
形成所有其他系统的主要结构支撑
there's no additional frame or chassis underneath
下面没有额外的框架或底盘
suspension
悬架
both front and back suspension setups share similar
前后悬架设置相似
upper and lower wishbone arms with a push or pull rod
带推杆或拉杆的上下叉骨臂
the wishbones
叉骨
are rigid structural supports
是刚性的结构支撑
with limited vertical travel
垂直行程有限
at the front where heat isn't an issue
在前面，热量不是问题
wishbones are directly attached to the monocock
叉骨直接连接到旋钮上
and have simple flexure joints
并有简单的柔性接头
designed to bend under load
设计用于在负载下弯曲
at the rear where engine heat can be intense
在后部，发动机的热量会很高
spherical bearings are used
使用球面轴承
the push or pull rod is where the action happens
推杆或拉杆是动作发生的地方
our model has push rods in the front
我们的型号前面有推杆
and pull rods in the back
并在后面拉杆
which simplified
这简化了
just indicates how the system is mounted
只是指示系统是如何安装的
to push or pull connected suspension parts
推或拉连接的悬挂部件
if parts can be mounted down low
如果零件可以安装得很低
for a lower center of gravity
为了降低重心
all the better
更好
the pull rod connects to a rocker and damper
拉杆连接到摇杆和阻尼器
which we call shock absorbers in normal cars
我们称之为普通汽车的减震器
but instead of large coiled springs
但不是大螺旋弹簧
F1
suspension uses a small metal rod called a torsion bar
悬架使用称为扭杆的小型金属杆
that twists under load
在负载下扭曲
one side of the torsion bar moves
扭杆的一侧移动
with the outer cylindrical shaft
带外圆柱轴
while the other side is stationary
而另一边是静止的
both independent suspension sides are linked
两个独立的悬挂侧是相连的
to a central roll bar
到中央滚动杆
that twists to limit body roll
扭曲以限制身体滚动
heave is the vertical position of the car
升沉是汽车的垂直位置
which is critically important for proper aerodynamics
这对正确的空气动力学至关重要
the heave spring and damper cleverly come into play
升降弹簧和阻尼器巧妙地发挥了作用
when both sides move up or down together
当双方一起向上或向下移动时
for example during acceleration or braking
例如在加速或制动时
but are mostly inactive for other movements
但对其他运动大多不活跃
the heave spring in our model is a stack of flexible
我们模型中的升降弹簧是一堆柔性的
cone shaped washers
锥形垫圈
that compress together under load
在负载下压缩在一起
washers can be added or subtracted for fine adjustments
可以增加或减少垫圈以进行微调
the front suspension handle similar tasks to the rear
前悬架处理与后悬架类似的任务
but with different techniques
但使用不同的技术
the steering system is closely packaged
转向系统包装严密
with front suspension
带前悬架
a track rod links each tire
履带杆连接每个轮胎
to a fairly standard hydraulic rack and pinion setup
一个相当标准的液压齿条和小齿轮装置
with the steering column extending into the cockpit
转向柱伸入驾驶舱
the rear suspension has a track rod as well
后悬架也有一个跟踪杆
for vertical tire angle adjustment
用于垂直轮胎角度调整
all wheels must be attached to the car
所有的轮子都必须连接到汽车上
with wheel tethers
带车轮系绳
these are strong cables
这些是坚固的电缆
that keep wheels connected to the car
使车轮与汽车保持连接
in the event of an accident
一旦发生事故
they're required
他们是必需的
to pass through more than one suspension element
通过多个悬挂元件
for increased safety
为了提高安全性
with few exceptions
除了少数例外
most exposed suspension elements
最暴露的悬挂元件
are either made from or bonded with carbon fiber
由碳纤维制成或用碳纤维粘合
for better aerodynamic forms
为了更好的空气动力学形式
this is another
这是另一个
major reason
主要原因
suspension parts are packaged inside bodywork
悬挂部件包装在车身内部
away from outside air wherever possible
尽可能远离外界空气
braking system
制动系统
a master cylinder and reservoir
主缸和储液器
controls and stores hydraulic fluid for braking
控制和储存用于制动的液压油
F1 cars have two master cylinders
F1赛车有两个主缸
and accompanying reservoirs
以及伴随的水库
for front and rear brakes respectively
分别用于前后刹车
the cylinders are mounted to the brake pedal on one end
气缸安装在制动踏板的一端
and a threaded brake bias screw on the other
另一个上有螺纹制动偏置螺丝
this bias screw is electronically controlled
这个偏置螺丝是电子控制的
and can be adjusted on the fly
并且可以即时调整
as directed by the driver
按照司机的指示
the screw position
螺丝位置
allows different pressure to the front or rear brakes
允许对前刹车或后刹车施加不同的压力
brake lines snake through suspension elements
刹车线蜿蜒穿过悬挂元件
to the brake caliper
到制动卡钳
and shoe assembly
和鞋组装
intense brake heat must be precisely managed
必须精确控制强烈的制动热
so the entire inner wheel assembly is covered
所以整个内轮组件都被覆盖了
by a ducted carbon fiber shroud
通过管道碳纤维护罩
the front wing
前翼
helps direct air into the brake ducts
有助于引导空气进入制动管道
and through the inner wheel for cooling
并通过内轮冷却
the calipers
卡钳
are mounted at the lowest possible position
安装在最低的位置
for proper brake bleed
适当的制动出血
that is ensuring troublesome
这肯定很麻烦。
air bubbles can escape hydraulic brake lines
气泡可以逃出液压制动线
while maintaining a low center of gravity
同时保持低重心
the brake discs
刹车盘
and shoes are made from a carbon based material
鞋子是由碳基材料制成的
the disc has thousands of small holes
圆盘有数千个小孔
extending from the center outwards
从中心向外延伸
for maximum cooling effects
以获得最大的冷却效果
the rear brakes have a similar design strategy
后刹车有类似的设计策略
that have become smaller in recent years
近年来变得越来越小
with the addition of the mguk
加上mguk
or motor generator unit kinetic
或电动发电机单元动力学
the mguk is geared to the crankshaft
mguk面向曲轴
and functions as an electrical power generator
并起到发电机的作用
to charge an onboard battery
为车载电池充电
as driven by a portion of rear braking forces
由一部分后制动力驱动
a computer mounted inside the gearbox enclosure
安装在变速箱外壳内的计算机
manages and balances this complex braking system
管理和平衡这个复杂的制动系统
the wheels are secured to the hub
轮子固定在轮毂上
with a single wheel nut
带单轮螺母
metal retention pins keep the nut securely in place
金属固定销将螺母固定到位
a specially designed wheel gun
一种专门设计的轮枪
pushes these pins down when removing the nut
卸下螺母时将这些销向下推
engine and associated systems
发动机和相关系统
F1 cars use six cylinders in a V configuration
F1赛车使用六个V型气缸
the pistons are somewhat flat and small
活塞有些扁平和小
to suit the high revving engine
以适应高转速发动机
intricate
错综复杂
exhaust headers feed a comparatively massive turbine
排气头供给一个相对较大的涡轮机
at the rear of the engine
在发动机的后部
which is part of a split turbocharger design
这是分体式涡轮增压器设计的一部分
that separates these normally stacked turbo components
将这些通常堆叠的涡轮增压组件分开
red hot exhaust gases drive the turbine wheel
炽热的废气驱动涡轮
which in turn spins the front mounted compressor wheel
进而旋转前置压缩机轮
drawing in and compressing huge quantities of air
吸入并压缩大量空气
all this pressure
所有这些压力
adds unwanted heat to the incoming air
给进入的空气增加不需要的热量
so one entire side pod is dedicated to the intercooler
所以整个侧吊舱都专用于中冷器
the path of incoming air looks like this
进入空气的路径是这样的
the compressor draws air in through an intake duct
压缩机通过进气管道吸入空气
mounted in the roll hoop
安装在滚圈中
above and behind the driver's head
司机头部上方和后面
hot air leaves the compressor towards the intercooler
热空气离开压缩机进入中冷器
side pod air rushes by the intercooler's tubes and fins
侧舱空气通过中冷器的管和翅片
cooling the compressor air inside
冷却内部的压缩机空气
the now cooled air
现在冷却的空气
passes through the special split ducting
通过特殊的分体管道
that feeds separate intake plenums
供给单独的进气室
these are chambers
这些是房间
designed to keep air pressure balanced
旨在保持气压平衡
between cylinders
气缸间
intake trumpets extend into the plenums
入口喇叭延伸到全会
for specially tuned air delivery to each cylinder
用于特别调整空气输送到每个气缸
the sidepod air flows by and cools the engine and
侧舱空气流过并冷却发动机
other internal parts on its way out
其他内部零件正在退出
the back of the car
汽车后部
the exhaust section of the turbo
涡轮增压的排气部分
has dual wastegates
有双重废物门
corresponding to each exhaust input
对应每个排气输入
to vent off excess gases when needed
在需要时排出多余的气体
wastegate pipes follow the main exhaust pipe
排水管顺着主排气管
out the back
从后面
a high tech heat recovery unit
高科技热回收装置
sits between these turbo compartments called
坐在这些涡轮增压舱之间
the mguh or motor generator unit heat
mguh或电动发电机组热量
excess heat from turbo gasses
涡轮气体的多余热量
drives this unit to act as an electric generator
驱动这个单元充当发电机
to charge the onboard battery
为车载电池充电
energy recovery system
能量回收系统
the mguh and the previously shown mguk together
mguh和之前显示的mguk在一起
make up the hybrid functionality of the modern F1 car
构成现代F1赛车的混合动力功能
both units generate electrical charge for the battery
两个单元都为电池产生电荷
once sufficiently charged
一旦充满电
the battery can send power back through the mguk unit
电池可以通过mguk单元将电力送回
which again is geared to the crankshaft
它同样与曲轴传动
in this way
以这种方式
the mg UK can generate an additional maximum
mg UK可以产生额外的最大值
160 horsepower
160马力
or as much as a small separate car engine
或者像一个小型独立的汽车引擎一样
various additional radiators for cooling
用于冷却的各种附加散热器
occupy the opposing sidepod
占据对方的侧翼
this includes the main engine cooling radiator
这包括主机冷却散热器
an oil cooler
油冷却器
and a battery cooler
和一个电池冷却器
an additional bank of radiators
一排额外的散热器
sits in the path of a separate roll hoop
坐在一个单独的滚圈的路径上
air duct
风管
to cool hydraulic oil
冷却液压油
gearbox oil and the MGU H&K systems
变速箱油和MGU H&K系统
F1 teams may locate specific radiators
F1车队可能会找到特定的散热器
in different positions
在不同的位置
than I've shown here
比我在这里展示的要多
though the general available spaces will be similar
虽然一般可用空间会相似
they may also use water driven
他们也可能使用水驱动
intercooling for turbo air
涡轮空气中冷
in contrast to the simpler air to air setup I've chosen
与我选择的更简单的空气对空气设置相比
fuel tank
油箱
the fuel tank also called a fuel cell
油箱也称为燃料电池
is a nearly puncture proof Kevlar bladder
是一个几乎可以穿刺的凯夫拉尔膀胱
lined with rubber
内衬橡胶
it occupies an isolated compartment in the carbon fiber
它在碳纤维中占据了一个独立的隔间
monocoque shell
硬壳
and fills all available space
并填满所有可用空间
F1 fuel cells can hold an incredible 30 to 40 gallons
F1燃料电池可以容纳令人难以置信的30到40加仑
of fuel
燃料
which is just enough for a single race
这只够一场比赛
as pit stop refueling is not allowed
因为进站加油是不允许的
these cars
这些车
get an estimated 4 to 6 miles per gallon of fuel
估计每加仑燃料能跑4到6英里
the tank has various internal baffles
水箱有各种内部挡板
with one way valves
带单向阀
to tame the sloshing liquid
驯服晃动的液体
under incredible racing forces
在难以置信的赛车力量下
the goal
目标
is to keep the large fuel mass centered and low
就是保持大燃料质量居中和低
and also to prevent foaming and fuel pump starvation
还可以防止发泡和燃油泵饥饿
the engine oil tank is placed between the engine
发动机油箱放置在发动机之间
and fuel cell
和燃料电池
gearbox
变速箱
the 8 speed gearbox 7 forward plus 1 reverse
8速变速箱7前进加1后退
sits behind the engine in its own aluminum cartridge
坐在发动机后面的铝制墨盒里
the rear differential gears connect to rear axles
后差速器齿轮连接到后桥
with special tripod joints
带有特殊的三脚架接头
that allow spinning axles to tilt
允许旋转轴倾斜
with the rear suspension movement
随着后悬挂运动
safety systems
安全系统
f1 cars have robust safety systems
F1赛车拥有强大的安全系统
the rear crash structure protects against rear impact
后碰撞结构可防止后碰撞
side crash structures
侧撞结构
are concealed within the aerodynamic bodywork
隐藏在空气动力学车身中
the removable front nose section handles front impact
可拆卸的前鼻部分处理前冲击
and the all important mono cock
还有最重要的单声道鸡巴
forms a protective cocoon around the driver
在司机周围形成一个保护茧
also attached to the monocoque
也附在硬壳上
a Halo device which was implemented in 2018
2018年实施的Halo设备
for additional driver safety
为了额外的驾驶员安全
and a roll hoop
和一个滚圈
the driver's helmet
司机的头盔
is kept
被保存
within a specific angle from the roll hoop to the body
从滚圈到身体的特定角度内
for maximum Protection
最大限度的保护
in the event of a rollover
在翻转的情况下
cockpit
驾驶舱
F1 racing seats are crafted from molds
F1赛车座椅由模具制成
taken from a specific driver's body
取自特定驾驶员的身体
the driver sits in a reclined position
司机坐在倾斜的位置
almost like laying semi upright in a hammock
就像半直立躺在吊床里
a 6 point harness keeps the driver in place
6点安全带将驾驶员固定在适当的位置
the seat
座位
wraps around the driver's body wherever possible
尽可能缠绕在司机身上
and safety structures surround the helmet area
和头盔周围的安全结构
drivers wear a special brace
司机戴着特殊的支架
called the Hans or head and neck device
叫做汉斯或头颈装置
to limit head movement in adverse conditions
在不利条件下限制头部运动
a connected strap clips to either side of the helmet
连接的带子夹在头盔的两侧
and the shoulder
还有肩膀
harness straps
背带
keep the device pressed against the driver
保持设备压在驱动程序上
a drinks tube extends over the shoulder
饮料管延伸到肩上
it's connected to a small fluid reservoir
它连接到一个小的流体储存器
to keep drivers hydrated while racing
让车手在比赛时保持水分
drivers use different
司机使用不同的
helmet front and rear spoiler designs
头盔前后扰流板设计
to keep their helmets from lifting
以防他们的头盔抬起来
or moving around
或者四处走动
with sometimes dramatically shifting air pressures
有时气压会急剧变化
in recent years the visor opening has further narrowed
近年来，遮阳板开口进一步缩小
to protect the more fragile visor area from puncture
以保护更脆弱的面罩区域不被刺穿
or breakage
或破损
cockpit design makes efficient use of
驾驶舱设计有效利用
all available space
所有可用空间
such that drivers must remove the steering wheel
这样司机必须移除方向盘
to exit the car
从车里出来
steering wheel
方向盘
this is the famed Formula 1 steering wheel
这是著名的一级方程式方向盘
drivers
司机
mostly don't need to remove their hands from the wheel
大多数人不需要把手从方向盘上移开
for steering so the wheel doesn't need to be round
用于转向，这样轮子就不需要是圆的
a customizable display at the center
中心可定制的显示
shows the current gear as the largest item
显示当前齿轮为最大项目
along with things like lap times
还有圈速之类的东西
tire and brake temperatures average speed and so on
轮胎和刹车温度平均速度等等
the daunting array of knobs
令人生畏的旋钮阵列
dials and LEDs
表盘和LED
gives drivers and teams fine controls
为车手和车队提供良好的控制
that can be adjusted on the fly during a race
可以在比赛中即时调整
clockwise from the upper left
从左上角顺时针方向
there's the Energy Recovery System dial
这是能量回收系统的表盘
to control the MGU H&K
控制MGU H&K
left and right menu navigation buttons
左右菜单导航按钮
a push to talk radio switch for team communication
用于团队沟通的一键通无线电开关
LED warning lights for critical systems
用于关键系统的LED警示灯
a row of LEDs across the top of the display
显示屏顶部的一排LED
acts as a Rev counter and shift light system
充当转速计数器和换档灯系统
the launch control switch
发射控制开关
which is turned on for race starts and off when racing
它在比赛开始时打开，在比赛时关闭
the brake balance dial for front and rear brake bias
前后制动偏置的制动平衡盘
a pit limits button
一个坑限制按钮
to automatically impose things like
自动强加诸如
pit lane speed and acceleration restrictions
维修站车道速度和加速度限制
an engine mapping dial
发动机映射表盘
to alter engine performance characteristics
改变发动机性能特性
Drs toggle button
Drs切换按钮
rear differential lock open or closed adjustment
后差速器锁打开或关闭调节
with separate turn entry and turn exit adjusters
带有单独的转弯入口和转弯出口调节器
the drinks dispenser button
饮料分配器按钮
more settings navigation buttons
更多设置导航按钮
three programmable preset dials for the engine
发动机的三个可编程预设转盘
chassis or suspension
底盘或悬架
and a scenario selector for things like wet weather or
和场景选择器，用于潮湿的天气或
tire preservation presets
轮胎保护预设
the neutral button is for neutral and reverse gears
空档按钮用于空档和倒档
which can't be selected with rear paddle shifters
无法使用后换档器选择
a message OK button
消息确定按钮
an overtake button
超车按钮
to instantly apply optimal settings for overtaking
立即应用最佳超车设置
and finally a hydraulic settings dial
最后是液压设置表盘
to control the complex hydraulic components
控制复杂的液压元件
spread throughout the car
遍布全车
for example in the gearbox and suspension systems
例如在变速箱和悬挂系统中
paddles at the back
后面的桨
of the steering wheel handle gear shifting up or down
方向盘手柄的上下换挡
the middle paddles are driver customizable
中间的桨是驱动程序可定制的
and both bottom paddles actuate the clutch
两个底部桨启动离合器
only one clutch paddle can be used for race start
只有一个离合器桨可以用于比赛开始
once in motion
一旦运动
the clutch isn't needed for gear shifting
换档不需要离合器
further down into the cockpit we see the gas pedal
深入驾驶舱，我们看到油门踏板
with contours to wrap around the driver's foot
有轮廓包裹在司机的脚上
so as to keep pedals completely separate
以保持踏板完全分开
and the brake pedal on the left
还有左边的刹车踏板
sensors
传感器
there are sensors all over these cars
这些车上到处都是传感器
for example
例如
a pilot tube at the front measures air speed
前端的导向管测量空气速度
the driver's custom molded ear plugs
驾驶员定制模压耳塞
have an accelerometer to track head movement
有一个加速度计来跟踪头部运动
there's a microphone at the rear
后面有麦克风
to pick up exhaust sound
拾取排气声
for size comparison
用于尺寸比较
here's our average height driver model
这是我们的平均身高驾驶员模型
standing beside an average sized car
站在一辆普通大小的汽车旁边
next to our formula model
在我们的公式模型旁边
it's important to note that
重要的是要注意
even with the level of detail
即使有详细级别
I've strived to attain here
我一直在努力达到这个目标
the complexity in F1 cars feels almost endless
F1赛车的复杂性感觉几乎是无穷无尽的
in a way that truly tested my research abilities
以一种真正考验我研究能力的方式
they really are incredible racing machines
它们真的是不可思议的赛车